ATTALIAHSIBUSISIWE NIKISI

Procurement Officer

38 Hoya Road, New Mabvuku, Harare, Zimbabwe. +263784501582 | +263715322445 +263737859868 attynikes@gmail.com 12/22/1996 | Single

MY CAREER GOALS

I would like to work with an organization where I can grow and gain more experience as a professional and be in a position where i can master the art of supply chain systems, finding mentors and becoming a mentor myself thus gaining exposure and getting to exhibit high levels of professional courage.

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

- Ability to train new staff and setup new systems that suite the changing trends of business.
- Inviting, very friendly, and engaging personality.
- Sound knowledge of administrative work.
- Helpful and polite.
- Good inventory management and organisational techniques.
- Good relationship with suppliers.
- Smart appearance and articulate.
- Good with Microsoft Word
- Business Retail Suite (retail manager software)
- Application of Company Standards and Policies
- Commercial awareness.
- Pro-active, good communication and teamwork.

CAREER HISTORY

May 2020-present

Butchery supervisor at TM Pick n' Pay Chain stores and Wholesalers

May 2019-May 2020

Buying Admin Clerk Attaché at TM Pick n' Pay Chain stores and Wholesalers Head Office Duties:

- creating allocation purchase orders for all stores
- providing analytical and clerical support to the buyers i.e. price listings, new supplier listings, new products listings, updating price entries for stores.
- providing reports for the buyers on stock valuations, sales statistics, stores stock holding and futures buy analysis.
- setting up and maintaining stock and supplier records.
- liaising with buyers on issues regarding prices and product detail i.e. case sizes, product listing descriptions
- reporting directly to the buying admin controller or the buyers on all issues i.e. stores queries, supplier price updates etc.
- preparing price comparisons and cost analysis and competitive retail strategies.
- maintaining buying authorisation files.
- filling documents in an orderly manner for futures reference.
- attending to incoming field calls and offering prompt, timely and courteous response to store enquiries.
- maintain confidentiality on all issues relating to the organisation, suppliers and fellow employees.
- providing suppliers with category sales data and market share information and what they can do to improve their sales.

March 2017-2018

Information Desk Assistant

Duties:

- Answering the phone and receiving all customers who have queries
- Assisting the customer care manager preparing quotations and hampers for the customers.

April 2016 - March 2018

Cashier at TM Pick n' Pay Chain stores and Wholesalers Duties:

- handled cash, cheques, and credit and debit card transactions with customers.
- scanned goods and collected payments from customers.
- issued receipts, refunds, and change to customers.
- redeemed stamps and coupons and gave candies in times of shortage of change.
- resolved customers complaints.
- kept accurate and complete record of daily transactions.
- scanned and logged in prices of products on the system.
- developed customer engagement and provided excellent customer experience.
- registered ringing and general cash handling.
- operated computer and handled cash transaction as per Company directives.
- was able to meet Company standards in relation to merchandising, housekeeping, security, and loss prevention requirements.
- assisted in counting incoming goods from suppliers and controlling inventory.

EDUCATION:

Harare Polytechnic: Certificate in Purchasing and Supply Management

Current Studies: Diploma in Purchasing and Supply

High School: 9 O'Level passes including English and Maths

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Reading | Cooking | Traveling | Movies

REFERENCES

Mr F Sandinga
Buyer TM Pick n Pay
194 Mutare Road, Msasa
Harare
fsandinga@tmsm.co.zw
+263 242 447255-73 ext. 2084

Mr J Kondo

Buyer TM Pick n Pay 194 Mutare Road, Msasa Harare jkondo@tmsm.co.zw +263 242 447255-73 ext. 4031